http://www.4icj.com/privacy/

Toggle navigation Home
Top 100
World Top 100 Job Sites World Top 100 Job Boards World Top 100 Recruiters & Headhunters World Top 100 Temporary Staffing Agencies
Top Job Sites by Country
Top Job Sites in North America Top Job Sites in Latin America Top Job Sites in Europe Top Job Sites in Asia Top Job Sites in Oceania Top Job Sites in Africa Top International Job Sites
About
About Us Ranking Methodology Contact us
Search
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We care about your privacy and we follow the OECD Privacy Guidelines
Information about our Organisation and Website
Our principal activity is: International directory and search engine of job sites and career resources
Our privacy policy covers jobRank.org and its web site:
Organisation Name:
jobRank.org
Address:
Suite 2C, 5 Tambua Street
City, Zip:
Pyrmont, 2009
State:
NSW
Country:
Australia
Controller:
F a b i o  F a t u z z o
Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access
You can access our web site home page and browse our site without registering, signing up or disclosing your personal data.
The services and links of our web site
Our Web site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.
Automatic Collection of Information
We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.
We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. However third party service providers, such as Google Analytics and Google AdSense, may use cookies and other various tracking technologies.
Data Collection and Purpose Specification
We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations.
To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please see below. We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.
Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal data from children at any time.
Disclosure and Visitor Choice
We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.
Confidentiality and Security
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:
unauthorised access
improper use or disclosure
unauthorised modification
unlawful destruction or accidental loss
We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.
Privacy Compliance
Our privacy policy is compliant with the following instrument: Australian Privacy Act - www.privacy.gov.au
In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure.
Table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used
The following primary personal data are volunteered by each visitor while filling contact or other forms in our website.
Primary personal data
Website Technical Administration
Research & Development
Customer Administration
Marketing
Trading in personal data
Name
x
Access to the personal data we may hold about you
You can ask us by email. We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a month, although we may before require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge. We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.
Twitter
Facebook
Google+
Copyright © 2001- 2020 jobRank.org All Rights Reserved About us Privacy
